cosplay.com 2018-03-28

# 

**Updated August 10, 2011**

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested, by linking to it at the bottom of each page of the website.

This privacy policy only applies to Cosplay.com. This policy does not apply to any website linked to from Cosplay.com. Cosplay.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of any website linked to from Cosplay.com.

**The Information We Collect:**

On some pages, you can register for an account, upload photos, and interact with other users. The types of personal information collected at these pages may include your IP address, your browser and version, your operating system and any additional information you willingly provide to us. We collect aggregate information on what pages users access or visit.

All of this information is stored in our log files and/or databases.

When you register for an account, you are asked to provide a valid email address.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for a period of time. Cosplay.com uses cookies to simplify member login and to facilitate navigation through the password protected areas of the website. Cosplay.com also uses cookies for customization of content, storing login information and statistical site-traffic analysis. Advertisers that appear on Cosplay.com may place cookies on your computer. Please visit their sites to learn about their specific privacy practices, as Cosplay.com does not have control over their policies. Advertisers and other companies do not have access to Cosplay.com’s cookies. This privacy policy does not cover the cookies used by any of our advertisers.

**The Way We Use Your Information**

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website, to customize the content and/or layout of our site for each individual visitor, to notify you of updates to our website, to communicate with you, and to conduct internal research on site usage and trends.

We do not share, sell or disclose your email address to third parties. You also have the option to opt-out of receiving administrative emails from our server. We retain the right to email you in any case where it is absolutely necessary.  
Cosplay.com aggregates anonymous information to compile demographics which may be shared with other services or companies. None of this aggregate information contains any personally identifying information. 

We may share your personally identifying information if you specifically allow us to share it, such as opting in for more information on a specific product or service.

We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us, protect and defend our rights, or protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others.

In the event Cosplay.com becomes part of another organization either through acquisition, sale of assets or merger, your user information and all personally identifying information may be transferred the successor entity, and your information would remain subject to the pre-existing privacy policy.

**Third Party Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Publicly Posted Information**

As a registered user of Cosplay.com, you have the option of posting information and content to our forums, your user profile, and other locations on the site. Some of this information may be re-assembled and presented in various formats around the website, such as user photo galleries and search results.

Your profile may also show statistics of your site usage, including your join date and date of last visit. Additionally, some content you post on Cosplay.com may reference the date it was posted. All of this information is publicly available.  
Cosplay.com is not responsible for the use by others of any information or content that you have made publicly available through your posting on our website. All user content that you post is done so at your own risk.

**Changing Your Information**

You may review the personally identifiable information we collect by logging in to your account and editing your information in your user control panel. This panel gives you access to add, modify, correct and delete your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

You can delete your account from Cosplay.com by sending a private message to the administrator with the request.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

Our servers are located in a physically secure facility, and only pertinent employees and agents are given access. All passwords are encrypted. Cosplay.com does not have access to your password and can only assist you in creating a new one. Please remember to select a password that cannot be easily guessed and we advise you to protect your password from disclosure. If you suspect any unauthorized use of Cosplay.com’s website, please contact us with the information.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. We do not allow anyone under the age of 13 to register for an account.

We strongly advise minors 13 years of age or older to ask their parents for permission before posting any information about themselves anywhere on the internet.

**Updates**

From time to time we may update this privacy policy. When this policy is updated, the changes will be posted to this page. It is up to you to periodically check this page for updates. Any significant changes will be posted in an announcement on our website.

Revisions to the privacy policy become effective the date they are posted. Your continued use of this website constitutes an acceptance of the updated privacy policy.

If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, your only remedy is to remove your account from our website. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please mail us at the following address:

Cosplay.com, LLC  
9811 W. Charleston Blvd. STE 2-540  
Las Vegas, NV 89117
